Hello friends, today we are going to talk
about a new investment plan of ICICI Prudential which is
for pure leverage investment income, so let's complete
today's discussion, now we will discuss
about this policy, what
features are given to you in it and what are the benefits in it
and after taking it,
what kind of returns are you going to get in it, this time we are going to
talk on this topic, first of all I would like to
tell you about the features of the benefits in this policy, if you
like then you
can subscribe for Rs. 1000 in it and you are getting it
with the subscription,
so let me explain to you
what benefits you get in the features Swadesh policy,
in this policy
you get life insurance, okay, the
life insurance benefit is given to you in it
along with the guarantee,
this means if you check on this policy then
you will get interest on your investment in this policy after some experience, after
15 years or after 20 years, after
25 years  Brother, you start earning around the age of 30, which
means it is guaranteed that this
carat income, in this, income carat means a
value is told to you, when you purchase from the policy,
then you are told only one thing that you are going to get
this money every year and for
how many years you are going to get it, you can install any one of these options from the option,
this number, right now,
what happens in Choice of Subscription, on one hand you are doing it at the minimum, the
money you will get in return from
this policy will come as income,
you are taking it back after the completion of the policy, so that
company starts the subscription, if
you want this above, then this
more
subscription means you will get it and when
that
subscription ends, then do
it properly, so
we will cover this in this video, that is
why we are doing it, in
one lesson I will tell you about tax rebate in
which you can take
and I would like to tell you one thing, in this policy
you have a lot of emergency
response of money, in this you get Option D
for taking loan, so how much loan can you get
and how straightforward it is, we are talking about it  In
this video also we are going to talk about this,
so now we will talk about the plan's glass on this, that is, we will take a look at
this pass again,
what is the business explanation in it, the
header of the options page, this plan, as I
told you, is with the income option and come with dowry
accused, if you do income options
Abhinandan, then in this you
get the facility of one tour, in both there is the
same option, you can do it on the seventh tour
before 2018, for this you get these options,
income rate
means after taking the policy, you have to decide for how many years
you want to get such income,
in both the plans also you will get 15
years, 2013, 2533 years, so that much you will get
income, if you do less of this then
you will get a little more,
in income if you reduce the profit, that is, if you increase it then the
obesity will reduce, that is, this is what you
want,
you get
incomplete only for so many years and there is a point in starting the income that
your payment will end
or else  If
you want to grow your company,
you should tell me how much you should have to subscribe to this side.
In this video,
if you
subscribe, then the
terms which are
given in it are twenty three years
2838,
means every six years, if you subscribe in it, then you
can take this 6 years, if you are doing it
first, then in that also you should
subscribe to the
policy
whose age is the
minimum maximum exact match road, that is,
when your policy is matched,
what should be your age, it can also be 10 years, it can also be 60 years,
this is straight,
okay,
60 years or
more, okay, so
subscribe, then subscribe to this channel, so
now what will we do,
in this, after
completion of
medium
subscription,
you will get income, it is not that
in this, but you are not like this, due to which you
get some time after the completion of the policy premium, like see, if you have
used seven years, you have money and out of that,
15%, if you have used the option in it, now this is the
phase, you have to take income options.
80 Anybody can select anything,
after this measurement is done on seven times,
your Noida appointment will start getting over soon for 8 years, 9 years
and
after it gets over,
your
last date to wake up is
15th January 2018,
then
subscribe for Rs.
1500 and start,
if any gift is
given to you on phase-1, I am
looking for you after Noida near, then
understand that you are doing this for half a year and you have to give
love along with it, when you buy your policy,
from there nine surveys will be completed, then
you will get these more commission, the
people of the village of the Sangh,
subscribe to the channel, so
if he is
doing this, okay,
understand Smita ji, this is thirty five
years old, and he gets about one
lakh rupees every year on PM, so if he chooses
option seven, then he has to do this for
more years, if he does this for
15 years, if he is
blind, then
he should
subscribe to that, that is, subscribe to the score
Example, if
you liked the subscription,
then
you
must watch this video, you should take the
decision only after the video ends, whether you want to take this 50 inch or
not, so right now
if I were in your place and I would take this aspect
or not, I will tell you,
first let us know about all these features, so for
this example, let
me explain it in a little detail, suppose now the year
2015 2022 is ok, today you have taken it from the call, ok, these
benefits, Chinese 1 lakh bigha
policy premium and but the payment which you have chosen,
you have
chosen the facility of making the payment after 10 years and they should
get pension for 30 years, ok,
subscribe to it, only then you will come to know
that you will get the money, so see in this, first year
B.A.  First year, second year, newly appointed for 10 years, it does
repair work, okay, so
as I had confirmed to you that if there is
tempered glass then the end of 12 years, after that
you have to
subscribe here
and
subscribe to the
channel, if
you commit suicide then we will talk about it, in this you who is the person, if
someone dies during the policy then life insurance
benefit is higher of,
whichever is higher out of these two, that is the time limit,
every tempered glass, that is,
whatever
you are doing, you should
subscribe to it,
subscribe to this video channel, this picture was
for seven years, okay, that is zero,
but this is Times and
Electronic, okay, you have taken it for ₹5, from
there you can
subscribe,
in the village you are
getting more subscription in it,
but you are
getting this money in it, but now the
school should
subscribe, Quid Chetram is getting more
that if you were appointed for example by the father for
10 years
In Palace sorry I forgot to tell you here it is
9720 so
subscribe to it and it may
not be available for subscription
then
subscribe to the channel
you
subscribe to
[music]
youth
then they
need first year professor 10 okay when
internet service service
then
they
mean total
subscribe so
look at this wait a bit
life insurance benefit in this benefits in
computer first you have to subscribe to
[music] subscribe subscribe and subscribe
then I will tell you
like
subscribe and then
subscribe to the channel
subscribe
that you stop Pinguwa premium if you will
stop paying after taking more now
with the mop it is decided in the policy that
if you had
subscribed
on this appointment
appointed commission appointed appointed appointed
try
subscribe and
subscribe then the policy will lapse if you do not
use it then you will not get anything okay
means if you do not use it for two years then you will keep
the points but reduce
means
whatever money you have subscribed to the company
means you will subscribe and
you are getting that subscription  If
you mean school
then you will
subscribe to this
subscription of appointments,
you will get that much subscription, take that 50% from me, you will get it
in the range of Rs. 5870, you have more
appointments,
you have 2 years patience and
subscribe, so what do you think how much
money will you get, subscribe
to
subscribe, let me tell you that you should
know that there is war, but some such things keep happening that there is
war, so understand that if you compare the
benefit with other, then your
benefit will be less from here, that is the
first thing
you
need, okay, that means school
and
subscribe to your friends, if you want to
start then subscribe to this company,
then
subscribe to the score,
in Pushpa year you have to restart the polish,
sir, it is a product, okay, if
your policy lapses then it will be
cancelled from there, then you
get time, okay, you get any speed, at
that speed if you do not smoke,
okay,
very soon, so for that
subscribe to the appointed village channel, if you subscribe
to my channel,
if you
subscribe for
15 years, I will appoint you, then that will be till then  If
you get any credit tips then we will
give you it, okay so
this is the thing,
okay
you should subscribe
to these four tips, if we are getting them done then
you will
ask this,
subscribe,
if you need money then no
one will
subscribe to [music], if
not then no one will give it and I will give it after seeing this,
but you will get the loan as
much as you have taken, then you should
subscribe to the audio, that
means to get a school policy, subscribe to this channel,
okay so you
need to
subscribe to this channel,
so I have given you 180 rupees to my friend by
subscribing, okay, if
your interest increases, if you do
not return the money then the companies will give you a
plus policy, okay, on the side there is 20 percent, that
means you will have 20% of the surrender value, that
means if you cancel then you are getting this SIM,
okay, for that question
subscribe, if you
subscribe
but you
cannot take any benefit in this,
I will
tell you in this video,
now we will see
with a complete example, I will tell you in very simple language
that complete example  What happens,
suppose you want to buy it from the bank, okay, you
should take this policy, suppose you have
₹5000, you can deposit it on every branch, so for
example, I can deposit ₹15000 every year
on the African land every year for 10 years, okay, then
I can deposit ₹15000 every year, which means I am going to give 5 lakhs
to the company, so this will become
my policy, I have
subscribed 786, means if you have not subscribed till now, then
please
subscribe
because you will get complete
merit of life insurance policy from this till 5th,
I have to pay this for 10 years,
which will be 12 years,
from Devvand, I bought it in the purse, from there till 5th, it will be
submitted, then if you get it properly, then
subscribe, then
how much
benefit is there in the score,
means you are
getting more than 300 rupees, but
how much money does the company get,
means I am getting
5 lakh rupees in the school, now
how much money have you deposited with the companies, 5 lakh
rupees and the company will give you Chautala
with high income, okay  So in this you see when you take out a
policy, first you
prepay ₹50, then 4.7 subscribe to it,
₹50, so this
subscription of yours means
you have to
subscribe for the appointed subscription, after that
subscribe and in the second you
cannot subscribe for 1.27 if you
pay income tax, otherwise there is no problem,
but these benefits happen because,
okay, so this is the
owner of this, Mr. okay,
okay, subscribe to this channel, I am going to take
my
picture
and
subscribe for it, so this is
installment
subscription, you have
not bought your policy, this is absolute
soon, okay, now
I am telling you that this is the policy option, at least
subscribe, subscribe,
subscribe,
first
subscribe
button,
here the
company starts its 80,
that they are getting money from this, okay, here you are getting
money, so okay, that is
more for you, okay, so see here, okay, you are getting
this money, here you
get the police post, 12 years, 13, 14 years
subscribe, okay, you will get this, so
one means
subscription, so I
told you that the
youth
If you
subscribe with this, do
not forget to subscribe to the channel
and how do you have to do it,
means if you have minimum surrender value,
you are getting 125000 here interactive here,
you have
subscribed, if you want to subscribe to someone then
definitely subscribe,
how much will you get by subscribing to the channel,
total five,
this channel
subscribe
button, this deposit at this time in this video
I will tell you the link in the description box,
video must be
Dhishoom Guarantee Tomorrow For, what happens,
I will tell you in the description box of this video
and I will tell you about these people
appointed here,
so here this
subscribe subscribe
subscribe, okay,
you see,
see here how much one and a half, friends,
welcome to the new, most powerful criminal,
how much 10 lakh have you given, how much are you getting,
how much are you getting, your
intellect, okay, you are getting this much, so
these were two options, so
I have brought you another example, that is not
of 50,000, which you can see in the options,
this is appointed
here,
appointed, so
in this  You are getting
₹5000 for subscribing, like subscribing and subscribing, if it becomes
possible that now this will be seven or six for you, then it will be
hot soil, so the interest has
not been decided, so in this, I
mean if you mean if you subscribe to the company totally,
and on
top of the subscription, how many
subscribers should you
subscribe to the channel and the
appointed magnet, and there were others, you will
not get anything, the card is
over,
example, in this you will see how much your favorite, on the
first and second side,
see these less 10
appointed here, in this, if you melt here
[music],
you said
how much profit you are getting, okay,
surrender value, so this is the calculation, so
if you have to see this chart,
how simple will you get, if you
choose whatever amount, how much money will you get,
so I will tell you this link, okay,
here
in expenditure, okay,
if you open it, the first such link will come, okay,
first limit it,
okay, as the first link will come,
press the home button on Om here, after going to home,
see the like and subscribe
button mission here, in this
Click on continue,
this is through disinvestment, you can buy
our juice for the birthdays of celebrities here,
then do some canteen, okay
now see here you have an option, if you
want to play by selling how much,
you will
cover all the idlis, click on it, you have to do it only
for 70 years, ₹10 note has to be changed to ₹15, that
means it is required for 15 years, now you should subscribe to this channel and
share it,
okay if you subscribe then
see here, download and
subscribe here, then
see here, it will come here,
how much money are you getting as a policy benefit, it will be done
for this, you
would like to tell here
which policy you are installing, it should be
told here how much money will you get, how much will you get, how much did you get,
all this calculation will be shown by default here,
now after understanding so much,
you are feeling that if I want to reach your place, if I do
n't want to, then I would
definitely have bought this polythene because
this money is giving itself to a better option than this, you are feeling that
so much money is being spent by you.
How much money are you getting,
it can be even half of it, okay so why bother about this, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel in the video description
then quickly press the subscribe button, thank
you